是只飞兽！
It's a flying beastie!
嘿，你们，站住！
Hey, you! Stop!
散开！
Scatter!
- 飞行员说什么了？  - 跑道上有个警察亭
- The pilot said what?
- A police box on the runway.
说得跟真的似的！让他回到排队区
A likely story! Tell him to get back into stack
等待下一步安排
and await further instructions.
Rock 小姐，接机场警局
Miss Rock, get the airport police.
控制台呼叫SDX
Control. Sugar Delta X-ray.
请返回排队区
Return to stack.
警局吗？我是总指挥
Police? Commandant here.
入港航班报告说有障碍物
In-bound aircraft reports obstruction
说是在第五和第二跑道的交界处
on intersection of runways five and two.
去调查一下，汇报情况
Investigate and report back.
警察亭子
Police box.
Jamie！到我这里来
Jamie! Come over here with me.
快来
Come on.
等一下
Just a minute.
把信封给我
Give me that envelope!
我建议你站住
I would advise you to stop.
啊！
Agh!
你能快点过来吗？有麻烦了
Can you come quickly? Trouble.
麻烦？发生什么事了？
Trouble? What happened?
那些明信片，有人发现了
The postcards. Someone found them.
就来
Right.
行了，行了
All right, all right.
那你们是把它卸在四号机库了，但它是个什么东西？
So you dumped it by number four hangar,
but what was it?
还真是个警察亭子？
It WAS a police box?
给我接警察总长
Get me the police chief.
好了，你可以安排那些飞机降落了
All right. You can bring those planes down now.
- 障碍已经被清除了  - 好的，先生
- The obstruction's been cleared. - Right, sir.
你觉得这是不是一个恶作剧，先生？学生什么的？
Do you think it was a practical joke, sir?
Students or someone?
不管他是谁，一旦被我抓到了，有他们好果子吃
Well, whoever it was, they'll pay for it
when I get my hands on them.
我可不能让这些恶作剧什么的威胁到乘客的生命
I won't have passengers' lives
endangered by practical jokers or anyone else.
Reynolds 警司吗？我让总指挥接您电话
Superintendent Reynolds?
I have the commandant for you.
警局总长
The Chief of Police.
听着，跑道上的警察亭子是怎么一回事？
Listen, what's all this
about a police box on the runway?
哦...好吧，各处的安保工作必须加强！
Oh. Well, security's got to be tightened up all round!
他报告说有人看到四个嫌疑人从那个亭子四散跑开
He reports that four suspects
were seen running away from it.
- 他们抓到了没？  - 没有！
- Did they catch them?  - No!
这些警察够笨的，这都能跑丢，这会儿都跑出八百米远了
Idiot of a policeman lost them.
They're miles away by now.
给我接出入境检查站
Get me Immigration.
跟他们说我想知道有没有人看到些可疑人员
Tell them to let me know
if any suspicious characters are seen there.
- Polly 在那儿！  - Polly！这边来！
- There's Polly!  - Polly! Over here!
博士...
Doctor...
我刚刚看到有人被害了！
I've just seen a man killed!
- 被一个飞兽给撞了？  - 不是
- Hit by one of the beasties?  - No.
刚才那里面有两个人
There were two men in there.
有一个人手里有枪，他开枪杀了另外一个
One of them had a gun,
and he shot the other one.
那个凶手，他看到你了吗？
The murderer, did he see you?
他还追我，但我设法甩掉了
He chased me but I managed to lose him.
你还能找到那个机库吗？
Could you find this hangar again?
这，我觉得能...
Well, I think so...
我还记得名字，好像叫变色龙什么的
I can remember the name.
It was Chameleon something or other.
- Ben 去哪儿了？ - 我们没看见他，先去找那个机库
- Where's Ben?
- We haven't seen him. Let's find this hangar.
那个有枪的家伙还会找我
The bloke with the gun will be looking for me.
我们会照顾你的，来，快点
We'll look after you. Now, come on.
- Ben 怎么办？  - 我们会找到他的，快点 //
- What about Ben?  - We'll find him. Come on.
- 他发现了那些明信片  - 他叫什么名字？
- He found the postcards.  - His name?
我不知道。我在办公室逮住他的
I don't know. I caught him in the office.
他已经发现了证据，我不得不阻止他
He'd found evidence. I had to stop him.
你杀死的是 Gascoigne 督察，是个警察
You've killed Detective Inspector Gascoigne -
a policeman.
你觉得他上面有人派他来的？
Do you think a parent sent him?
很有可能。不过没关系
Possibly. It doesn't matter.
重要的是没人会找到他
The important thing is that nobody should find him.
安排人处理掉吧
Arrange disposal.
好了，尽快搞定这事
All right. Get it over here as quickly as possible.
- 箱子已经在来的路上了  - 好
- A container is on the way.  - Right.
销毁这个
Destroy this.
你为什么把那些行李箱留在这里？
Why have you left those suitcases there?
那个侦探 - 我被他打断了
The detective - he interrupted me.
Spencer!​
Spencer!
看
Look.
那家伙是从那个门里出来的
The bloke came out of that door there.
被锁住了吗？里面有人吗？
Is it locked? Is anyone in there?
是锁住的，里面没有人
It's locked. There's nobody there.
那个开枪杀他的家伙
This man who killed him.
你还能认出他来吗？
Would you recognise him again?
能！他还追我，我怎么都能认出他来
Yes! He chased me. I'd recognise him anywhere.
愚蠢！
Fool!
Polly，你说说他是怎么被杀的？
Polly, how would you say he was killed?
用的是枪
With a gun.
你能给我描述一下吗？
Can you describe it to me?
不能，太远了。为什么？
No. It was too far away. Why?
这人是被电死的
This man was electrocuted.
他的衣服都烧焦了
His clothes are all scorched.
绝对是某种枪，博士
It was definitely some kind of a gun, Doctor.
有可能，但这种枪在这个地球上还没有研发出来
Maybe. But not one that's
been developed yet on this planet.
这个他们成为博士的人，他是从那里了解到这些的？
This man they call Doctor,
where does he get his knowledge?
他看起来像是一个普通人
He looks like a normal being.
比s大多数的智力高多了。他对我们的行动是一个威胁
More intelligent than most.
He's a threat to our operation.
- 我去杀了他  - 不，先抓那个女孩儿，她能指认你
- I'll kill him.
- No. Get the girl. She can identify you.
我们可以稍后再对付这老头
We can deal with the man later. -
- 他会说出去的  - 那又怎样？
- He may talk.  - So?
没人会信他的
Nobody will believe him.
我们必须向当局报告这个事情
We must report this to the authorities.
那个追杀我们的人，我们也许可以找到他
That man who chased us. We could find him maybe.
什么，警察吗？
What, the policeman?
不，不，Jamie。我们必须找到这个地方的总负责人
No, no, Jamie, we must find
the man in charge in this place.
那他怎么办？我们不能把他扔在这里
What about him? We can't just leave him here.
我们做不了什么了
There's nothing else we can do.
我们现在还是去找机场主楼吧，快点
Now let's find the main airport building. Come on.
你确定这条路对吗，博士？
Are you sure this is the right way, Doctor?
看起来是通向主楼的
It seems to lead to the main airport building.
- 我怎么了？  - 短暂的肌体失能
- What happened to me?  - A temporary disablement.
你很快就能恢复正常，起来吧
You'll be back to normal any second now. Up here.
- 你要带我去哪里？  - 你马上就知道了
- Where are you taking me?  - You'll see.
- 我抓住她了  - 很好，这次没人看见你吧？
- I've got her.
- Excellent. Did anybody see you this time?
她走在她朋友的后面，他们也没注意
She was following behind her friends,
but they didn't notice.
- 他们会来找我的  - 坐下
- They'll come looking for me.  - Sit down.
凶手！
Murderers!
你必须给我们放尊重点，回答我的问题
You'll have to show us some respect
and answer my questions.
- 你在那个航线上工作？  - 我没明白
- Which airline do you work for?
- I don't understand.
你肯定属于某条航线，或者这里的机场管理方
You must belong to an airline
or the airport authority to be in this area.
我跟机场没有任何关系，只是刚抵达这里，迷路了
I've got nothing to do with the airport.
We'd just arrived. We were lost.
我正想找人帮忙，然后就看到他杀了一个人
I was trying to find someone to help me,
and I saw him kill a man.
你说你们刚抵达这里？你怎么到这里的？
You say you'd just arrived? How did you get here?
我们从她这里问不出什么来
We'll gain nothing by questioning her.
重要的是我们抓住了她
The important thing is that we've got her.
你们不会觉得我的朋友们就这样把我给忘了吧，是吗？
You don't think my friends
are just going to forget me like that, do you?
我搞不懂了，博士，那儿都找不到 Polly
I don't understand it, Doctor.
Polly's nowhere to be seen.
她肯定出什么事了
Something must have happened to her.
这里锁住的，Jamie，里面没人
That's locked, Jamie. There's nobody there.
我担心我们是在浪费时间，Jamie
I'm afraid we're wasting our time here, Jamie.
我们越早找到当局越好，赶紧把情况告诉他们。快点
The sooner we find the authorities
and tell it to them, the better. Come on.
嗯，你说得对。你的朋友们的确在担心你
Yes, you're right.
Your friends ARE worried about you.
那我们就做点什么让他们不要继续担心了
Then we shall have to do something
to stop them worrying.
看起来是往这边，Jamie
This seems to be the way, Jamie.
打扰了。我们在找这里的负责人
Excuse me. We're looking for someone in authority.
等一下，先生。迟早到你
Just a moment, sir. All in good time.
谢谢你，女士
Thank you, madam.
好了，先生，请出示你们的护照
Now, sir. Your passport, please.
我没时间说这个，我们要找负责人
I've got no time for that.
We want to see someone in authority.
我就是负责人。请出示你的护照
I am in authority. Your passport, please.
我们有一些重要情况要报告
We have something important to report.
可以，先生，但得等你们找到了护照再说。下一个，请上来
Yes, sir, when you've found your passport.
Next one, please.
- 护照是什么？  - 官方那些繁文褥节。看！
- What's a passport?
- Official mumbo-jumbo. Look!
我们刚刚在那边发现了一具尸体
We've just discovered a dead body out there.
你听到我说话了吗？
Did you hear me?
听到了，先生。如果我是你，就会通知警方
Well, sir. If I were you, I'd inform the police.
请告诉我在哪里可以找到他们
Please tell me where we can find them.
在大厅里应该就有一个警察
There's probably a policeman in the main concourse.
- 大厅在哪儿?  - 从这个门过去往左拐
- And where is that?
- Through this door and turn to your left.
谢谢，非常感谢。走吧，Jamie
Thank you, thank you very much. Come on, Jamie.
我能看看你的护照吗，先生？
May I see your passport, sir?
我们俩谁都没有护照，你满意了吗？
We neither of us have passports!
Does that satisfy you?
我想你肯定搞错了，先生
I think you must be mistaken, sir.
你没有护照是不可能登上飞机的
You couldn't have got on the aircraft without passports.
- 什么飞机？  - 你们坐着抵达这里的飞机，先生
- What aircraft?  - The one you arrived on, sir.
我们不是坐着飞机抵达的
We didn't arrive on an aircraft.
好了，听着，这个玩笑开得有点过头了
Now, look here, this joke's gone far enough.
你我都知道，你们肯定是搭乘最后进港这个航班抵达的
You know and I know that you must have arrived
on the last inbound flight
- 而这个729航班来自马德里  - 告诉他 TARDIS 的事情
- which was flight 729 from Madrid
- Tell him about the Tardis!
- 那是什么？  - 是我们到达这里的方法
- What's that?  - It's the way we got here.
你们两位绅士不会碰巧知道一个警察亭子吧，知道吗？
You gentlemen wouldn't know anything
about a police box, would you?
我说的就是这个。我们就是...
That's what I'm saying! We're...
我真的觉得我们的交通方式跟这个无关
I really think that our mode
of conveyance is irrelevant.
重要的事情是我们在外面发现了一具尸体！
The important thing is that
we discovered a dead body out there!
而我们想把这事报告给这里的负责人！
And we want to report it to someone in authority!
我想你们有很多机会跟负责人见面
I think you'll have plenty of opportunity
to see someone in authority.
- 好，谢谢你，非常感谢  - 你们能坐一会儿吗，那边
- Well, thank you. Thank you very much.
- Will you take a seat, over there
给我接总指挥，谢谢
Give me the commandant, please.
你好，长官。我是Jenkins, 出入境五号柜台
Hello, sir. Jenkins here. Immigration desk five.
我这里有两个你说的嫌疑人员
I've got two of your suspects here.
这里有人吗？
Anyone here?
这附近应该有人啊。这里有人吗？
There must be someone around. Anyone here?
哈罗，Blade 机长在吗？
Hello. Is Captain Blade about?
我不知道，我有点迷路了
I don't know. I'm a bit lost.
你是在找我吗？
Are you looking for me?
是的，我这里有你的飞行排班表，都安排好了
Yes, I have your flight schedules here.
They're all in order.
- 谢谢    - 再见
- Thank you.  - Goodbye.
- 你有什么需要吗？  - 我在找出口
- What do you want?  - I'm looking for the way out.
这里是私人物业，不欢迎游客
This is private property. Visitors are not welcome.
你是机场方面的吗？
Do you belong to the airport staff?
是，我今天刚上班
Yeah. I started today.
我不是故意来这里的，只是走迷路了
I didn't mean to come in here. I got lost.
- 你确定？  - 当然确定
- Are you sure?  - Of course I am.
你还打算带我出去不？
Are you going to direct me or not?
当然，来吧，我给你指路
Yes, of course. Come on. I'll show you the way.
你说这个女孩儿目击了异常谋杀？
You say this girl witnessed a murder?
那人被一把射线枪给电死了
He was electrocuted with a ray gun.
- 一把什么？  - 哦，是什么枪又有什么关系
- A what?  - Oh, what does it matter what sort of gun.
关键是他被杀了，而我的朋友又目睹了事情经过
The point is he was killed and my friend saw it happen.
那你朋友在哪儿？我想跟她谈谈
Where is she? I'd like to talk to her.
这个，又是另外一件事了，她消失了
Well, that's another thing. She's vanished.
哦，消失的人，射线枪。这是某种玩笑吗？
Oh, people who vanish, ray guns...
Is this some sort of joke?
如果你见到尸体就不会觉得这是个玩笑了
You wouldn't think it a joke if you saw the body.
他们是坐哪趟航班来的？
What flight did they come in on?
哦，长官，他们是跟马德里729航班的乘客一起进来的
Well, sir, they came in with the passengers from
flight 729 from Madrid,
但他们没有护照
but they've no passports.
也许你们可以解释一下，你们为什么没有护照
Perhaps you'd kindly explain why you have no passports.
哦，天，我们完全是在浪费时间！
Oh, look, we're all wasting time!
你们还去不去看尸体了？
Are you going to come and see that body, or am I
或者是我得去找这个地方真正的负责人？
going to find someone
who really is in charge in this place?
我就是这里的负责人，谢谢
I am in charge of this place, thank you.
现在，你们俩立刻陪我去这个机库
Now, you both accompany me to this hangar immediately.
谢谢，非常感谢你。终于！
Thank you! Thank you very much. At last!
- 把我的去向告诉航空控制台  - 是，先生
- Tell Air Traffic Control where I am.  - Yes, sir.
这里是出入境五号柜台
Immigration desk five here.
一号已经刚往机库去了，他期望我告诉你们这个信息
Number One's just gone to the hangar area.
He wanted me to let you know.
事实上，他是去找一具死尸
As a matter of fact,
he's just gone to look for a dead body.
是啊，总会有这么一天的，对吧？
Yes, It's gonna be one of those days, isn't it?
- 搞定她了？  - 她已经被处理了
- Get her?  - She's being processed.
下一航班他们可以再带一个了
They can take another on the next flight.
很好
Excellent.
尸体它 - 不见了！
The body - it's gone!
- 你能肯定就是这个机库？  - 是，名字都在外面呢
- You're quite sure you've got the right hangar?
- Aye. The name's up outside.
尸体刚才就躺在这里
The body was lying just here.
那，那我们看看能找到什么，行吗？
Well, let's see what we HAVE got, shall we?
你到底是在做什么？
What exactly are you doing?
当然是在帮警察找线索。问题在于我没法告诉他们那人是谁
For the police, of course.
The trouble is I can't tell them who he was.
某种神秘人物，肯定无疑
Some sort of mystery man, no doubt.
是的，事实上他真是
Yes, as a matter of fact he was.//
他口袋里没有任何东西可以表明他的身份
There was nothing in his pockets to identify him.
- 一个口袋里没有任何东西的人  - 是的，我也觉得很诧异
- A man with nothing in his pockets
- Yes, I was rather surprised myself.
- 等等，里面还真有个东西  - 他口袋里有什么？
- Wait. There WAS one thing.
- What did he have in his pocket?
这个
This.
- 一张邮票  - 但它是西班牙的，而且还没有用过
- A postage stamp
- But it's Spanish and it hasn't been used.
噢，这我就觉得有很大的不同了
Oh, I'm sure that'll make all the difference.
的确。哈罗...这有点意思
Exactly. Hello... This is interesting.
你现在发现了什么？
What have you found now?
一丝被烧焦的纤维
It's burnt fibres.
这说明什么，博士？
What about this, Doctor?
刚才这里并没有，这里有个烧焦的痕迹
This wasn't here before. It's a burn mark.
你说的对，Jamie，这是新的
You're right, Jamie. It's quite new.
能见到有人肯动动脑，真是高兴
It's good to see someone is using their intelligence.
噢，我受够这些了！你们俩跟我来
Oh, I've had enough of this!
You two coming with me.
绝对是射线枪造成的
Definitely made by a ray gun.
射线枪，烧焦的纤维，外国邮票
Ray gun, burnt fibres, foreign stamps...
- 没用过的外国邮票 - 好，没用过的外国邮票
- Unused foreign stamps.
- All right, unused foreign stamps.
我肯定是跟你一样疯了，还在听你瞎说！
I must be as mad as you are,
even to be listening to you!
- 你知道他们把它怎么样了么？  - 把什么怎么样了？
- You know what they've done with it?
- Done with what?
尸体。在某个地方肯定有一个很大的行李箱
The body. Somewhere there's a large packing case.
就在你后面，博士
Right behind you, Doctor.
- 需要我帮忙吗？ - 你是变色龙观光团的吗
- Can I help you?
- Are you connected with Chameleon Tours?
是的，我是机长Blade，首席飞行员
Yes. I'm Captain Blade - chief pilot.
这两位绅士觉得这里发生了一个事故
These gentlemen think
there's an incident happened in here.
- 一个事故？ - 你介意我们看一下这个行李箱里面吗？
- An incident?
- Would you mind if we have a look in this packing case?
- 冒昧问一下，你是哪位？ - 我是机场总指挥
- May I ask who you are?  - I'm the commandant.
可以，当然可以
Yes, of course.
你们指望找到什么呢？
What do you expect to find?
一个死人
A dead man.
真有意思
How very interesting.
塑料杯！
Plastic cups!
现在我得做点自己的调查工作了
Now I'm going to do some investigating of my own.
我很高兴终于激起了你的兴趣！
I'm glad I've roused your interest!
哦，的确是，不过我打算调查的是你
Oh, you have. But what I'm going to investigate is you.
还有你俩为什么会出现在机场
and why you're both here in the airport.
谢谢你，Blade 机长。来吧，你俩，出去
Thank you, Captain Blade. Come on, you two. Out.
我们最好迁就一下他
We'd better humour him.
把他弄下来
Bring him down.
好了
It's all right.
- 他能活下来吗？ - 如果我们动作快点
- Will he survive? - If we hurry.
就这里了
There you are.
我们得把你弄到机场大楼去，这样你就安全了。
We've got to get you to the airport building
and you'll be safe.
你快要到窒息点了，快点
He's reaching suffocation point. Hurry.
你都没有让我好好搜查//
You didn't let me search properly.
那个机库出租给了一个私有承包公司
That hangar is leased to a private charter company.
我无权在那里进行搜查。
I've have no right to search in there.//
现在，你可否坐下来，保持安静？
Now, will you kindly sit down and keep quiet?
Jenkins，给我接 Reynolds 警司
Jenkins, get onto Superintendent Reynolds.
这是他的活儿，这些人在这里乱闯
This is his job. These people are trespassing.
- 我这里刚有另外一家飞机抵港  - 好吧，我自己来
- I've just got another flight coming through.
- All right. I'll do it.
博士，你看！
Doctor, look!
- 总指挥，这就是我刚跟你说的那个女孩  - 再说一遍？
- Commandant, this is the girl I was telling you about.
- I beg your pardon?
你认识这两位先生吗？
Do you know these gentlemen?
- 不认识，怎么了，该认识吗？ - 据他们说，他们认识你
- No. Why? Should I?
- According to them, they know you.
- 你去哪儿了，Polly？  - Polly？
- Where have you been, Polly?  - Polly?
我不叫 Polly， 你们肯定搞错了
My name isn't Polly. You must have made a mistake.
我这辈子从没有见过他们
I've never seen them before in my life.